<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE pkgmetadata SYSTEM "http://www.gentoo.org/dtd/metadata.dtd">
<pkgmetadata>
	<maintainer type="person">
		<email>PF4Public@users.noreply.github.com</email>
	</maintainer>
	<upstream>
		<remote-id type="github">microsoft/vscode</remote-id>
		<bugs-to>https://github.com/microsoft/vscode/issues</bugs-to>
		<doc>https://github.com/microsoft/vscode/wiki</doc>
	</upstream>
	<longdescription>
		Visual Studio Code - Open Source
	</longdescription>
	<use>
		<flag name="api-proposals">Enable API proposals !WARNING! Enabling them might be forbidden by Microsoft licensing terms!</flag>
		<flag name="badge-providers">Allow various badge providers</flag>
		<flag name="build-online">Disable network-sandbox and open Pandora's box!</flag>
		<flag name="electron-19">Build against electron-19 instead of the default one. Use at your own risk!</flag>
		<flag name="electron-20">Build against electron-20 instead of the default one. Use at your own risk!</flag>
		<flag name="electron-21">Build against electron-21 instead of the default one. Use at your own risk!</flag>
		<flag name="electron-22">Build against electron-22 instead of the default one. Use at your own risk!</flag>
		<flag name="electron-23">Build against electron-23 instead of the default one. Use at your own risk!</flag>
		<flag name="electron-24">Build against electron-24 instead of the default one. Use at your own risk!</flag>
		<flag name="electron-25">Build against electron-25 instead of the default one. Use at your own risk!</flag>
		<flag name="electron-26">Build against electron-26 instead of the default one. Use at your own risk!</flag>
		<flag name="electron-27">Build against electron-27 instead of the default one. Use at your own risk!</flag>
		<flag name="electron-28">Build against electron-28 instead of the default one. Use at your own risk!</flag>
		<flag name="electron-29">Build against electron-29 instead of the default one. Use at your own risk!</flag>
		<flag name="electron-30">Build against electron-30 instead of the default one. Use at your own risk!</flag>
		<flag name="electron-31">Build against electron-31 instead of the default one. Use at your own risk!</flag>
		<flag name="electron-32">Build against electron-32 instead of the default one. Use at your own risk!</flag>
		<flag name="openvsx">Use Eclipse Open VSX instead of Visual Studio Marketplace</flag>
		<flag name="reh">Build Remote Extension Host</flag>
		<flag name="reh-web">Build Remote Extension Host for Web</flag>
		<flag name="substitute-urls">Even though telemetry is disabled by default in this ebuild, one might want to replace telemetry reporting urls with 0.0.0.0</flag>
		<flag name="temp-fix">Enable this if vscode does not build for you by default, this could help</flag>
	</use>
</pkgmetadata>
